YEA YEA YEA
yeah yeah
DAMN RIGHT BRO!
4 AM IM JUST GETTING STARTED
FOR MY BIRTHDAY I THREW
ME A SURPRISE PARTY
REMINISCING ABOUT THE TRAP
PLAYING THE FIRST CARTER‚
MY LIFE CHANGED WHEN I
HAD MY FIRST DAUGHTER
GOT MY FIRST QUARTER FLIPPING
50 DOLLAR SLABS
YOU NIGGAS LOOKING AT THE BILLS
ASKING YOU FOR HALF
CUT FROM A DIFFERENT CLOTH‚
TAKE PRIDE IN RESOURCE‚
ANYTIME SHE WANNA DIP IM
PROVIDING THE SAUCE
YOU ON SIDE OF THE BOSS‚
SO YOU KINDA THE BOSS
YOU KEEP PLAYING WITH ME I
END UP SIGNING YOUR BOSS
DROP AN EP ON A NIGGA‚ FOR
THE FREE FREE ON A NIGGA
YEA YOU ZZ ZZZ ON A NIGGA‚ KING
LIKE BB ON YOU NIGGAS
ROCK WITH CHAMPAGNE P‚ IF IT
WASN′T FOR THE STRUGGLE
THEN I WOULDN′T BE ME
CALL ME DEUCE OR DOS‚
ANYTHING BUT BROKE
GOT MY AIM FROM THE SCOPE‚ GOT
THE GAME BY THE THROAT. YEA
OK YOU POPPED UP ON ME BY SURPRISE
YOU SEE I NEVER TOOK YOU
FOR THE POPPIN TYPE
DAMN it is 4AM SO PLEASE
BELIEVE THE HYPE
HIT THE LIGHTS IM WAY OVERTOP‚
POP IT FLICK IT
DROP A PIN SEND A LOCATION
IMA PULL UP IN THAT BULLET
PROOF SPACESHIP
DROP OFF A BAG OF SOME DANGEROUS
IMA HIT U 4 AM SEE IF YOU MAKE IT
OHH I DROPPED COLLEGROVE OUT THE SKY
OHH IN A GROUP WITH THE BEST
RAPPER THATS ALIVE
OHH NEVER TURN MY BACK ON MY SLIME
OHH I AINT WANNA FUCK THE
BITCH BUT SHE WAS FINE
OHH HOLD UP BABY LET ME TAKE MY TIME‚
OHH HARD TO GET SOME HEAD
AND TRY TO DRIVE
OHH JUMPING OUT THE CAKE
AND THATS SURPRISING
OHH PICKING UP THE DUFFLE
BAG LIKE EXERCISING
OHH BOUGHT MAMA A NEW HOUSE
COS SHE DESERVE IT
OHH PRACTICE MAKES PERFECT
BUT NOBODIES PERFECT
OHH ESCOBAR IS NOW OPEN FOR SERVICE
OHH SEND YOU TO DR MIAMI
FOR YOUR SURGERY OHH
OK YOU POPPED UP ON ME BY SURPRISE
YOU SEE I NEVER TOOK YOU
FOR THE POPPIN TYPE
DAMN it is 4AM SO PLEASE
BELIEVE THE HYPE
HIT THE LIGHTS IM WAY OVERTOP‚
POP IT FLICK IT
DROP A PIN SEND A LOCATION
IMA PULL UP IN THAT BULLET
PROOF SPACESHIP
DROP OFF A BAG OF SOME DANGEROUS
IMA HIT U 4 AM SEE IF YOU MAKE IT
OHH RICARDO TISCI ON THE CREWNECK
OHH ON A KILLING RAPPER SPREE
AND NIGGA YOU NEXT
OHH THEY TALKING CHILLING
WATCHING NETFLIX
OHH I USED TO TRAP AND WATCH BOOTLEGS
OHH IM ON MY WAVE LIKE A DURAG
OHH I SEE YOUR BOO NOW
WHERE YOUR CREW AT
OHH TALKING TEQUILA FOR THE PIPE UP
OHH I HOPE YOU GOT A CLEAN VAGINA YEA
DRENCH GOD DRENCH GOD REALLY
REPRESENTING WE THE SQUAD REALLY
TEK GOT THE ROLLIE NOW LETS GET IT
I USED TO SELL DRUGS FOR A LIVING
GOT ME A JOB SELLING RECORDS
HAD TO USE MY JEWELER FOR A REFERENCE
MIGHT BUY A CHARM WITH THE EXTRAS
MIGHT USE HER LEGS FOR A NECKLACE
OK YOU POPPED UP ON ME BY SURPRISE
YOU SEE I NEVER TOOK YOU
FOR THE POPPIN TYPE
DAMN it is 4AM SO PLEASE
BELIEVE THE HYPE
HIT THE LIGHTS IM WAY OVERTOP‚
POP IT FLICK IT
DROP A PIN SEND A LOCATION
IMA PULL UP IN THAT BULLET
PROOF SPACESHIP
DROP OFF A BAG OF SOME DANGEROUS
IMA HIT U 4 AM SEE IF YOU MAKE IT